http://www.cshardware.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Custom Service Hardware wants to assure you that we are very careful about how we run our site. We take our customers' satisfaction and privacy seriously.
Our Web Site
This web site is owned by Custom Service Hardware, Inc. You can access our web site at the following address:www.cshardware.comWe have created our web site to provide additional services to our customers and potential customers online.
What Information We Collect-
Your nameYour billing and delivery addressYour e-mail addressYour phone (or mobile) numberYour credit/debit card numberInformation on how you are using the SitesYour purchase/return/exchange information
Name and Address
When you supply us with your postal address online, you may occasionally receive catalogs and mailings from us with information about products, promotions or services. If you do not wish to receive these mailings, please send us a note, along with a copy of your mailing label to the address below:Custom Service Hardware1170 N Wauwatosa RdCedarburg, WI 53012Or, e-mail us your name and mailing address to service@cshardware.com
Occasionally, we make a portion of our mailing list available to respectable organizations that may interest our customers. If you do not wish to receive these mailings, please send us a note saying so, along with a copy of your mailing label to the address above - or send us the information in an e-mail to service@cshardware.com.
E-Mail Address
When you supply us with your e-mail address in an online form, we may send you a periodic newsletter with information about our web site and other promotions. To remove yourself from the email list follow the instructions included in the email. To be added to this list, please fill out our subscriber form. We never share your e-mail address with third parties.
Phone and Fax Numbers
When you supply us with your phone or fax number online, we may use them to contact you regarding an order you sent, or a question you asked. We never share these numbers with other organizations.
Credit Card
Sensitive information such as credit card numbers are protected by a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and are fully encrypted.
Cookies and Other Technologies
Cookies – These are small text files that are stored directly on your computer. They make it easier for the server to recognize your computer as you click from page to page (to keep track of your shopping cart as you browse our site, for example).
GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation)
Residences of the EU have the following Rights provided by the GDPR.
The right to be informed;
The right of access;
The right of rectification;
If you are a EU resident and would like to either have your data, update your data, or have your data removed please contact CSH with the information above.
Pixel Tags – these are very tiny images (smaller than the periods in this paragraph). They are there to inform our web server or e-mail server that you have opened an e-mail, for example, and to communicate other actions.
CS Hardware's website, online services, interactive applications, e-mail messages, and advertisements may use 'cookies' and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of our communications and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.
CS Hardware may also use cookies and other technologies to 'remember' how you use our website, online services, and applications. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience with CS Hardware more convenient and personal. For example, knowing someone using your computer or device has shopped for a certain product helps us make our e-mail communications and product suggestions more relevant to your interests. You may set your web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. However, should you decide not to accept cookies from our sites, you will limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our sites.
As is true of most websites, our web servers gather some information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to understand and analyze trends, to administer the site, to learn about user behavior on the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. CS Hardware may use this information in our marketing and advertising services.
Pixel tags enable us to send e-mail messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us whether mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to customers.
Children's Online PrivacyWe recognize the particular importance of protecting privacy where children are involved. We are committed to protecting children's privacy and we comply fully with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). CSHardware.com will never knowingly request or collect personal information from any person under 13 years of age without prior verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that an individual is under the age of 13 and has submitted any information to CSHardware.com, for any purpose without prior verifiable parental consent, we will delete his or her information from our files.
By interacting with CS Hardware, you consent to our use of information that is collected or submitted as described in this privacy policy. We may change or add to this privacy policy, so we encourage you to review it periodically.
